<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Raffaele Spataro</title><link>https://www.raffaelespataro.it/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Raffaele Spataro</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.raffaelespataro.it/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Large language models as theories of language</title><link>https://www.raffaelespataro.it/posts/coding/large-language-model-as-theories-of-language/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.raffaelespataro.it/posts/coding/large-language-model-as-theories-of-language/</guid><description>In this post, as part of a (potential) series, I will be sharing my thoughts on the latest technology and scientific advancements in a non-technical manner.
Large language models, such as ChatGPT, are not just mere software implementations. They are a representation of a language theory, which can be considered a scientific advancement. Like other theories that may not be &amp;ldquo;true under all circumstances,&amp;rdquo; language models have the potential to advance both science and technology.</description></item><item><title>Creating a Wikipedia Search and Summary Program Using OpenAI, Trafilatura, and Langchain</title><link>https://www.raffaelespataro.it/posts/coding/langchain-wikipedia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.raffaelespataro.it/posts/coding/langchain-wikipedia/</guid><description>Introduction In this tutorial, we will be building a Python program that searches for a specified topic on Wikipedia, extracts the text from the top search result, and generates a summary using OpenAI and Trafilatura. We will use the LLMChain library to connect these different functionalities.
Required Libraries We will be using the following external libraries:
loguru trafilatura openai langchain Before we dive deeper, ensure that all these libraries are installed in your system.</description></item></channel></rss>